The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Am I
qualified enough now ?
Fellow cultivator, wait !
Based on your strength, we are unable to stop you
from entering the pavilion.
However,
I need to ask if Fellow Cultivator has any connection with the Xu Family
of Planet Dong Lin.
If Fellow Cultivator Xu
is not from Dong Lin,
then on behalf of my Chen Family,
I would like to invite you
to become a non-family Elder !
Resources, spells,
we will not be stingy !
The pavilion's gate hasn't appeared yet.
The method to open it should be in their hands.
Now is not the time to complicate the situation.
What do you think,
Fellow cultivator ?
Maybe.
We'll discuss it after I leave the pavilion.
Alright !
You two,
help me to open the door !
May Fellow Cultivator
obtain a celestial fate
and return with a good harvest !
As expected,
this pavilion requires the combined efforts of multiple families to open.
The level of your celestial fate
is decided by the will of the heavens.
Touch my palm
to test your fate.
It's beginning...
Do you really intend to invite him as a non-family Elder ?
Of course.
If he joins my Chen Family,
I would like the two of you to pretend
that you don't know
what happened to Fellow Cultivator Yao
and find another explanation
to hide this matter.
Is he really worth your respect ?
He's courageous, resourceful,
and has powerful artifacts.
If he can serve us,
that would be icing on the cake !
Since he entered the pavilion
with a Corporeal Yang cultivation,
he'll get spells of the fourth floor !
Rank 8 Greater Celestial,
you can enter the fourth floor
to test your luck for a celestial spell.
It seems my cultivation
only allows me to enter the fourth floor.
Celestial fate...
If we're talking about celestial fate,
it might be worth a shot.
Greetings Celestial Lord, you can inspect the celestial spells.
Not bad.
I wonder what celestial spell this person
will obtain on the fourth floor.
Fifth floor !
What !?
Sixth floor !
Seventh floor !
Eighth floor !
This...
Our families' ancestors who set up the pavilion's restrictions
only reached the eighth floor at best !
No one
has ever reached the ninth floor !
What he'll obtain is...
celestial spells of the ninth floor !
Call the Wind
Summon the Rain
Magic Arsenal
Lands Collapse
Mountains Crumble
Dark Moon
Clear Skies
What does this mean ?
Illusions ?
They're all illusory objects.
Had I known this,
I would've gone to the fourth floor.
Greetings Celestial Lord,
you can inspect the celestial spells.
Does the word "inspect"
have deeper meaning ?
And where are
the celestial spells ?
This painting isn't still !
Nothing can be carried out of an illusion...
The secret
lies in this technique.
It's the tree from the painting !
I'm...
inside the painting !
Call the Wind
Summon the Rain
Magic Arsenal
Lands Collapse, Mountain Crumble
Dark Moon, Clear Skies
The pavilion-opening ceremony is about to begin.
Let's go see it.
Hurry !
The Collection Pavilion ?
Collection Pavilion
This is...
the Ancient Thunder Celestial Realm !
Master Carefree
Rank 9 Celestial King
It's him !
I never imagined
that I would witness Senior Master Carefree painting with my own eyes.
Indeed !
Today really is a feast for the eyes !
Marvelous !
Such abundant celestial spiritual energy !
The opening of the Collection Pavilion
is a joyous occasion for our Celestial Realm.
I, Celestial King Carefree,
offer this painting as a gift.
In this painting...
Why isn't the boy there ?
Bai Fan,
now that you've become the Celestial Emperor,
Celestial Emperor !?
you mustn't be stingy
on a day like this one.
We pay respects to the Celestial Emperor.
Bai Fan
Thunder Celestial Emperor
Early stage Nirvana Void
Carefree,
your temperament
still hasn't changed.
Since I have contributed,
you, the Celestial Emperor,
must also contribute.
Disciple,
what do you think this painting lacks ?
Qing Shui
Thunder Celestial Lord
Peak late stage Nirvana Shatterer
Master,
this painting has a tree but no wind.
Its shape is complete, but not its spirit.
Why don't
you give it a spirit
with Call the Wind ?
Brilliant !
Very well.
I shall seal the Call the Wind spell in this painting.
I'll seal it
on the ninth floor of the Collection Pavilion.
The spell within the painting
is the seal of the pavilion's core.
It will wait for the fated one
to comprehend this opportunity
and inherit this spell.
Since you have entered this painting,
you are the fated one.
Celestial spells are mysterious.
They can summon the wind and the rain,
turn anything into your soldiers,
collapse the lands and crumble the mountains,
or make a dark moon rise in a clear sky.
My first spell
is named Call the Wind.
Call the Wind ?
Do you know
what the wind is ?
The greatest Daos are the simplest.
Wind
rises from a single reed.
It seems trivial and insignificant,
invisible and intangible.
But...
it can comfort living beings,
nourish all things,
and even help life to proliferate.
But the power of the wind
is by no means limited to this.
The power of the wind
can extinguish the flame of all souls,
break through the surface of things,
to shatter their bones,
Call the Wind
Celestial spell
and scatter their souls.
When you are able to harness this power,
then you can
Call the Wind.
This wind...
It's not only tearing apart my body,
but it's also
tearing at my Origin Soul !
So this is
the power of Call the Wind !?
Whether you can comprehend this Call the Wind spell
depends on yourself.
Fellow Cultivator, your visit to the pavilion
must have yielded great rewards !
Would you let us have a look
at a celestial spell
from the ninth floor ?
Call the Wind...
A celestial spell !
He really got a celestial spell !
Having an extra Elder
isn't as good as having a celestial spell.
His mind must still be in a daze right now,
it's a heaven-sent opportunity !
Now !
Steal the spell !
Call the Wind...
What !?
Nooo !
Using Call the Wind
consumes too much origin energy !
Perfect,
I need these two's Origin Souls,
to replenish my loss !
Continue retreating
and you might live !
Let's escape...
Don't...
Don't kill me !
We can negotiate...
One more left.
Fellow Cultivator !
If the four great families
learn of this,
the consequences will be terrible !
Spare my life,
and I can cover for you !
Offend the four families,
and you'll be as good as dead
in all of Allheaven !
The spell within the painting
is the seal of the pavilion's core.
The seal of the pavilion's core ?
Could it be...
Indeed !
Collect !
Since things have come to this,
I have offended all four great families.
Then I might as well
be more vicious.
Brother Li,
I have a plan.
I need your help.
a few days later
I hope
the four families will like this gift.
3 days later
Today,
Lu Hecheng
Lu Family member
Illusory Yin
I will surely reach the third floor of this pavilion.
Chan Pingnian
Chen Family member
Illusory Yin
Then I'll take a stroll on the fourth floor.
What's going on !?
Who...
Who did this !?
The fragment of the Collection Pavilion has been sealed off,
outsiders won't know of the accident.
But the four families' pavilion guardian elders are dead.
If the fact I stole the pavilion is exposed,
they'll fight me to the death.
We can't stay here long.
Brother Xu,
are you really not going to the fragment with
celestial spiritual energy fluctuations ?
There's something about these fluctuations
that feels off.
I'm not going.
I finished my matters in the Celestial Realm.
We should leave as soon as possible.
This trip has been bountiful
thanks to Brother Li.
Like the celestial spells of this Collection Pavilion.
Brother Xu, please keep them for yourself.
I'm too familiar with the saying
"holding a gem brings calamities".
Besides, Brother Xu saved my life.
This small favor
is hardly worth mentioning.
To leave the Thunder Celestial Realm,
we must go to the celestial gate at the far west
to open the passage with our Thunder Cauldrons.
It's far away,
no time to waste.
Celestial Welcoming Palace
Western fragment
Thunder Celestial Realm
It's open !
Get in quick !
The celestial treasure is mine !
Almost there...
It's so close...
Nirvana Void is the level above Nirvana Shatterer.
---
The cultivations families had classifications that outsiders didn’t know about. Like in the Alliance Star System, a rank 7 cultivation planet was the peak existence on the surface.
Rank 8 cultivation planets were very rare, so much so that the entire Alliance Star System only had three. As for the most mysterious rank 9 cultivation planet, there was only one in the entire Alliance Star System!
The cultivation families in the Allheaven Star System had similar classifications, but they focused more on history. Only long-lasting cultivation cultivation families could become an eternal existence in the Allheaven Star System.
In the Allheaven Star System, the most common were the cultivation families on the main cultivation planets of the four different domains. There was not much difference in their strength, and three or four cultivation families existed on each planet.
Above these cultivation families were the four great families with inheritances from the Celestial Realm. They were the most powerful force in the Allheaven Star System on the surface.
Above them are six families with even older inheritances like the Xiang Family of Planet Dong Lin and the Li Family of Li Yuan.
Just like how the Alliance System had a rank 9 cultivation planet, the Allheaven Star System also had a family that had survived even longer than that. This was a family that had been around since the primordial times. The primordial cultivation family was the true powerhouse of the Allheaven Star System, and it was extremely mysterious.
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
by a child's steadfast heart ?
Nascent Soul
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
stand in the way,
Soul Transformation
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
and ask this question to the sky.
Ascendant
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.